Nicki Minaj working with Trump admin on plight of Christians in Nigeria.
Either she's getting a check.
She was mad at the whole time.
She genuinely thinks that she's doing something good,
which, by the way, is why y'all need to have people around you that know more than you.
And by y'all, I don't just mean celebrities.
Everybody.
Everybody should have people around them that they can consult with,
that think differently than you,
that hold you in a place of values.
Just so you understand what's happening here with the plight of Christians in Nigeria,
there is a plight of Christians in Nigeria.
However, the U.S., what does that have to do with the United States?
The United States is using this as a ploy, as a proxy,
to find their way into Nigeria so that they can then find their way into the Sahel states of Burkina,
Faso, Mali, and Niger, who, as you know, are coming together to begin a process of Pan-Africanism on the continent.
They are taking back their resources from France.
They are saying, we are going to build our own infrastructures.
This undermines the global empire's goal.
And so they have to try and shut it down.
Now, we saw earlier this year with AFRICOM and that cone, that general who tried to say,
oh, you know, they got some problems going down in Burkina Faso.
They're continuing to try to make this happen the same way that they're making fetch happen in Venezuela right now.
When do we stop allowing ourselves to be used?
We're going to fight this out there.
Listen to your people.
Because I hit hard.
Billionaire.